妈，你放心好不好？
Mom,would you relax?
那里离这里有十条街 而且她是一个人在晚上走
That was 10 blocks from here,and she was walking alone at night.
我绝不会那样的
I would never do that.
妈，别担心了
Mom,come on,stop worrying.
这条街很安全，这栋楼很安全 没有任何东西…
This is a safe street. This is a safe building. There's nothing
天啊！你跑进来干什么？
Oh,my God! What are you doing in here?!
妈，我必须挂电话了！
Mom,I gotta go! IT gotta go!
天啊！
Oh,my God!
没关系，你尽管看报
That's fine,you just read the paper.
我要去拿个锅子
I'm gonna get a pot.
不是为了你
It's not for you.
好了，很好
Okay,that's fine.
看看漫画
Read the Family Circus...
享受一下幽默…
...enjoy the gentle comedy....
喔，我的天，我的天 我的天…
Oh,my God,my God,my God,my God....
门是开的
It's open,you guys.
有事吗？
Can I help you?
菲比还住在这里吗？
Does Phoebe still live here?
没有，但我可以帮你传话
No,she doesn't. But I can get a message to her.
好，告诉她 她老公来过这里
Great. Just tell her her husband stopped by.
她的什么？
Her what?
你怎么变出来的？
How did you do that?
六人行 第2季 第04集 菲比的丈夫
The One With Phoebe's Husband
真是不可思议，菲比 你怎么会结婚？
This is unbelievable,Pheebs. How can you be married?
我不是“结婚”的结婚 你明白吗？
I'm not "married" married,you know?
他只是个朋友 而且他是同性恋
He's just a friend,and he's gay...
而且他来自加拿大 他需要一张绿卡
...and he was from Canada,and he needed a Green Card.
我不相信你嫁给了邓肯！
I can't believe you married Duncan!
你怎么能不告诉我？ 我们什么事都告诉彼此
How could you not tell me? We told each other everything.
对不起，但如果我告诉你 你会批评我…
I'm sorry,but I knew if I told you,you'd get judgmental...
不会赞成
...and wouldn't approve.
我当然不会赞成！
Of course I wouldn't approve!
你爱死了那个同性恋
You were totally in love with this guy who,hello,was gay.
你到底怎么想的？
What the hell were you thinking?
瞧？你还以为她很爱批评呢
See? And you thought she'd be judgmental.
我并不爱他 我只是帮助一个朋友
I wasn't in love with him. I was helping out a friend.
他离开后你一整个月都没下床
When he left town,you stayed in your pajamas for a month.
我还看到你吃乳酪汉堡
And I saw you eat a cheeseburger.
有没有？
Well,didn't you?
也许有
I might have.
我真不相信你没告诉我
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
你会告诉我一切事情吗？
Like you tell me everything?
我有什么没告诉你？
What have I not told you?
我不知道
I don't know.
譬如说外面电线杆上的内衣…
The fact that the underwear out on the telephone pole is yours...
是你跟鲍比 在阳台上做爱时丢下去的！
...from when you had sex with Bobby on the terrace!
什么？
What?
谁告诉你的？
Wait a minute! Who told you?
你死定了
You are dead meat.
我不知道那是个大秘密
I didn't know it was a big secret.
不是大秘密 一点也不是
Oh,it's not big. Not at all.
比方说就像…
IKind of the same as,say...
长了三个乳头！
... I don't know,having a third nipple!
你有三个乳头？
You have a third nipple?
你这贱人！
You bitch!
秀一秀！秀一秀！
Whip it out! Whip it out!
没什么好看的！ 只是个小突起，没有用处
There's nothing to see! It's a tiny bump. It's totally useless.
你其他乳头有多种用途咯？
As opposed to your other multi-functional nipples?
我真不能信任你！ 你说那是个小包
I can't believe you! You told me it was a nubbin.
乔伊，你以为小包是什么？
Joey,what did you think a nubbin was?
听到了一个名字 就不会多想了
You see something,you hear a word,I thought that's what it was.
让我再看一看！ 对，让我们看你的小包！
-Let me see it again! -Yes,show us your nubbin!
乔伊拍过色情电影！
Joey was in a porno movie!
如果我要垮台 每个人都要跟我一起垮！
If I'm going down,I'm taking everybody with me!
老天！ 你拍过黄片！
-Oh,my God! -You were in a porno?!
当时我很年轻，只想找个工作
I was young and I just wanted a job.
但最后一刻我无法做下去
But I couldn't go through with it.
他们就让我演修影印机的人…
They let me be the guy who fixes the copier but can't...
但是因为有人在上面做爱 所以无法修理
...because there's people having sex on it.
真是狂野！
That is wild!
形状是什么样子？ 有没有长毛？
-What's it shaped like? -ls it hairy?
碰到了会怎么样？
What happens if you flick it?
有没有什么特殊功能？
So does it do anything,you know,special?
只要压我的第三个乳头…
Pressing my third nipple opens the delivery entrance...
就会开启纳尼亚王国（著名的儿童魔幻小说）之门
...to the magical land of Narnia.
在有些文化中 第三个乳头象征了男性雄风
In some cultures,having a third nipple is actually a sign of virility.
有最好的住所 女人绕着你跳脱衣舞
You get the best huts,and women dance naked around you.
这些文化 是否可能在美国中部？
Are any of these cultures,per chance,in the Tri-State area?
你真是博学多闻 有什么是你不知道的？
You know,you are so amazing. Is there anything you don't know?
茱莉好聪明！茱莉好特别！
Julie's so smart! Julie's so special!
她是不是晚上全副武装出去打击犯罪？
Does she put an outfit on at night and go out and fight crime?
我也希望你能与罗斯复合
I wanted you to hook up with Ross as much as you did.
但现在他与她在一起 你必须忘了他
But he's with her now. You'll have to get over it.
原来我必须忘了他
Oh,I'm going to have to get over it.
我不知道该怎么办 原来只要忘了他就好
I didn't know that's what I had to do. I just have to get over it.
我必须写在我的手上
I'm gonna have to write that down on my hand.
性感美女！ 你要干什么？
-Sassy lady! -Where are you going?
我要去见邓肯 今晚他要在公园溜冰
I'm meeting Duncan. He's skating tonight at the Garden.
他参加了冰上剧团
He's in the Capades.
在冰上表演？ 不，在碎石路上表演
-The lce Capades? -No,the Gravel Capades.
转得不会很快 史努比跌倒时非常好笑
The turns aren't as fast,but when Snoopy falls? Funny.
我不相信你竟然为他打扮
I can't believe you'd dress up for him.
你又要重蹈覆辙了
You're setting yourself up all over again.
好的，不是
Okay,no.
我去看他 就是为了能彻底忘了他
For your information,I'm seeing him so I can put those feelings behind me.
我这样打扮是因为…
The reason I'm dressed like this is because I think it's nice...
我要让我的同性恋丈夫有面子
...to look nice for your gay husband.
该死，没牛奶了
Darn it,we're all out of milk.
钱德，能不能给我加一点？
Chandler,will you fill me up here?
我懂了，因为第三个乳头？
I see,I see. Because of the third-nipple thing.
亲爱的，待会见
Okay,sweetie,I'll see you later.
待会见，瑞秋 再见，茱莉
-See you later,Rach. -Bye-bye,Julie.
别闹了！
Come on,cut it out!
我能问你一件事吗？ 好啊
-Can I ask you something? -Sure.
什么？
What?
对我说吧
Come on,talk to me.
你与男人交往花了最久时间…
What's the longest you've been in a relationship before...
才发生关系的是多久？
... having the sex?
什么？谁没有…？ 你与茱莉还没有…
Why? Who's not? Are you and Julie not?
你与茱莉还没有发生关系？
Are you and Julie not having sex?
技术上来说？
Technically?
没有
No.
是不是因为她很冷感？
Is it because she's so cold in bed?
或者她非常专横 感觉像是在学校？
Or because she's kind of bossy,makes it feel like school?
不！她很好 我们又不是什么都没做
No! She's great. And it's not like we haven't done anything.
我们做了很多事情 像是…
We do plenty of other stuff. Lots of other stuff like
不！别告诉我细节
No! Don't need to know the details.
不，只是…
No,it's just....
我的问题
It's me.
我一辈子只跟一个人上过床…
I've only been with one woman my whole life...
后来她变成了同性恋
...and she turned out to be a lesbian.
所以现在我很担心
So now I've got myself all psyched out.
就像是…
It's become,like,this...
这件事！
...this thing!
你一定以为我很怪
You must just think I'm weird.
不，我不认为很怪
No,I don't think it's weird.
我想…
I think,in fact....
你知道我怎么想吗？ 怎么想？
-ln fact,you know what I think? -What?
我觉得这很性感
I think it's sexy.
性感？
Sexy?
让我告诉你，身为女人…
Let me tell you something. As a woman...
没有任何事情…
...there is nothing sexier...
比不想要做爱的男人更性感
...than a man who does not want to have sex.
真的？
No kidding?
你知道我会怎么做？
You know what I'd do?
我会等待下去
I'd wait.
你会等待？ 没错，我会等待…
-You'd wait? -Absolutely. I would wait...
一直等待…
...and wait....
然后我还会再等下去
Then I'd wait some more.
真的？
Really?
我不管她怎么说 她多么想要，多么恳求你…
I don't care if she tells you she wants it,she begs,she pleads...
她说她要跟其他男人做爱…
...she tells you she's gonna have sex with another man
这只表示收到了效果
That just means it's working.
女人真的希望如此？
Women really want this?
比珠宝还要渴望
More than jewelry.
欢迎来到麦迪逊广场公园
你看起来真美丽！
Look at you! You look great!
真的？谢谢
Do l? Thank you.
你也是，闪闪发亮！
So do you. Sparkly!
真是很棒，冰上剧团主角先生
This is pretty wonderful,Mr. Major Capades Guy!
我记得当你扮演在罗杰先生的冰上的弗雷迪国王（儿童节目）时很可爱
I remember when you were just King Friday in Mr. Roger's Ice Is Nice.
你一直说我会成功的
You always said I'd make it.
我总是有这方面的怪才能
Well,you know,I'm kind of spooky that way.
啊，我想念你！
Gosh,I missed you!
我要换衣服 好的
-I'm gonna get changed. -Okay.
现在就要
Now.
喔！对，好的
Oh! Right. Okay.
冲刺！
Ole!
什么？
What?
斗牛士…
The Matador....
冲刺！
Ole!
亲爱的，你能不能拿一下？
Sweetie,can you hold this for a second?
对不起，你脸上有个考古学家
Sorry,you had a paleontologist on your face.
但现在没有了，没事
But it's gone now. You're all right.
嗨，各位
Hi,everyone.
我要谢谢你先前的指点
I wanted to thank you for our little talk before.
没问题！所以你要等下去？
No problem! So you're gonna go with the waiting thing?
我本来要等 但是后来我又跟乔伊谈了
I was going to,but after I talked to you,I talked to Joey.
很好，他怎么说？
Good. What did he say?
他要我战胜自己去做就行了
He told me to get over myself and just do it.
我衡量了你说的与他说的
I thought about what you said and about what he said.
照他的话，今晚我就能做爱
And his way,I get to have sex tonight,so....
我口袋里有什么东西？
What is this in my pocket?
什么，是乔伊的黄色电影！
Why,it's Joey's porno movie!
放出来看看！
Pop it in!
我不介意 只要你们愿意看…
I'm fine,if you're okay watching a video...
一大堆两个乳头的人
...filled with two-nippled people.
大家都在做爱 正是我想要看的
People having sex. That's just what I need to see.
做爱有什么不对？
What's wrong with people having sex?
这些电影很冒犯人…
Well,you know,these movies are offensive...
侮辱女人与女性…
...and degrading to women and females....
灯光总是很呆板
And the lighting's always unflattering.
莫妮卡，帮我一下 我不管，我要看乔伊！
-Monica,help me out here. -Hell,I wanna see Joey!
有没有故事？ 还是立刻就开始…
So is there a story? Or do they just start doing it right
别理会我
Oh. Never mind.
等一下 那是我见过最疯狂的打字测验
Wait a minute. That is the craziest typing test I've ever seen.
我只能说，她最好被聘用
All I say is,she'd better get the job.
看来是他被“聘用”了
Looks to me like he's the one getting the job.
我上场了
Here I come.
我要修理影印机
See,I'm coming to fix the copier.
但是我修不了 我在想：怎么办？
I can't get to the copier. I'm thinking,"What do I do?"
所以我只好看他们做爱
So I just watch them have sex.
然后我要开口了！
Then I say Here's my line!
这对送纸匣很不好
You know,that's bad for the paper tray.
干得好，老兄！
Nice work,my friend!
等一下，又有我的镜头了 这家伙屁股挡住我了
Wait,you see me again. Hang on,the guy's butt's blocking me.
我冒出来了，又来了 又来了，又来了…
There I am. There I am. There I am....
怎么回事？ 昨天你来找我
So what's up? You came to see me yesterday.
我需要跟你离婚
I kind of need a divorce.
喔…好
O...kay.
为什么？
How come?
其实我又要结婚了
Actually,I'm getting married again.
什么？
What?
我不知道要怎么说
I don't know how to tell you this.
我不是同性恋
I'm straight.
我不懂你怎么会是异性恋？
I don't understand. How can you be straight?
你又聪明又幽默…
You're so smart and funny...
而且举办很棒的奥斯卡派对！
...and you throw such great Academy Award parties!
我也一直这么告诉自己
That's what I kept telling myself.
但是到了某个程度 就无法再扯谎下去了
But you reach a point where you can't live a lie anymore.
你知道了多久？
How long have you known?
我想我一直知道 自己不是同性恋
I guess on some level I always knew I was straight.
我觉得我应该跟别人一样
I thought I was supposed to be something else.
我是个冰上舞蹈者 所有朋友都是同志，我要合群
I'm an ice dancer,all my friends are gay. I was just trying to fit in.
真的要跟一个女人结婚？
And there's actually a woman?
她叫黛博拉
Her name's Debra.
她是不是你的第一个女人？
Well,is she the first that you've been with?
我从来没告诉过你…
I've never told you this...
但在大学有一两次…
... but there were one or two times back in college when...
我喝得大醉，去了异性恋酒吧
... I'd get drunk,go to a straight bar...
醒来时身旁有个女人
...and wake up with a woman next to me.
我以为这是因为酒精的缘故 而且大学每个人都在摸索
I told myself it was the liquor,and everyone experiments in college.
当然
Sure.
现在我知道我没有选择 我生下来就是如此！
Now I know I don't have a choice. I was born this way!
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
嫁给一个人六年 以为自己很了解他
You're married to someone for six years and you think you know him.
结果一天他说： 我不是同性恋！
And then one day he says,"Oh,I'm not gay!"
我还是我
I'm still me.
你为什么在六年前 没有发现这件事？
Why couldn't you just have figured this out six years ago?
里面闻起来还是有猴子的味道
You know,it still smells like monkey in there.
我们又有话可聊了
That saves us the conversation.
今晚很好玩，但我累死了
This has been great,but I'm officially wiped.
我也是，我们该走了
Me too. We should get going.
不！你们别这样！
No! Come on,you guys!
现在才十一点半
Come on,it's only 1 1 :30.
让我们好好聊聊 我们最近都没有一起聊过天
Let's just talk. We never just hang out and talk anymore.
瑞秋，我们在一起只有聊天
Rachel,that's all we do.
也许我们是如此 但是茱莉呢？
Maybe that's all we do. What about Julie?
茱莉怎么样？
What about Julie?
你已经加入我们将近两个月了
You have been in our lives for nearly two months now...
我们还没有真正认识你
...and we don't really know you.
茱莉究竟是什么样的人？
I mean,who is Julie?
你喜欢什么？不喜欢什么？
What do you like? What don't you like?
我们什么都要知道
We want to know everything.
这可能要花一段时间
Well,that could take awhile.
所以呢？
So?
谁没有时间更认识茱莉？
Who here does not have the time to get to know Julie?
我有时间来认识茱莉
I got the time to get to know Julie.
我跟她很熟了 我能回去吗？
I know her pretty well. Can I go?
没关系
That's fine.
让我们从你的童年开始 你的童年是怎么样？
Let's start with your childhood. What was that like?
简单地说…
In a nutshell
你告诉了你父母吗？
So,have you told your parents?
还没有，应该没关系 他们都很酷
No,but it'll be okay. They're pretty cool.
我弟弟是异性恋，所以…
My brother's straight,so....
就是这样了
Here you go.
我还有一个问题
You know what? I just have one more question.
如果你早一点知道 而我也在你身边…
If you had figured this out sooner,and I had been around...
你想会不会是我…？
...do you think l would have been the one...?
不，别告诉我
No. Don't tell me.
我想不管什么回答 都不会让我更好过
I don't think either answer would make me feel better. Here.
我爱你，菲比
I love you,Phoebe.
所以你弟弟是异性恋？
So your brother's straight,huh?
说真的
Seriously.
我的二年级老师是托马斯小姐
and my second-grade teacher was Miss Thomas...
我的一年级老师是柯布小姐
...and my first-grade teacher was Mrs. Cobb.
葛布小姐？
Mrs. Gobb?
不，柯布，就像柯布沙拉
No,Cobb. Like cobb salad.
柯布沙拉里面究竟有什么？
What exactly is in a cobb salad?
我要回家了
I'm going home.
茱莉真是爱说话，嗯？
Boy,that Julie's a talker,huh?
晚安
Good night.
很晚了，你们大概没有打算…
It's pretty late. You're probably not still planning on....
我有
No,I am.
你紧张吗？
Are you nervous?
我以前做过
I have done it before.
你要如何进行？
I mean,how are you gonna handle it?
要先谈谈？还是直接猛扑上去？
Are you gonna talk about it beforehand? Are you just gonna pounce?
我不知道，我想我要…
I don't know. I guess I'm just gonna...
顺其自然
...see what happens.
祝你好运！
Good luck!
什么？
What?
没事…
Nothing....
这是你与她的第一次 如果第一次就不顺利…
It is your first time with her,and if the first time doesn't go well...
那就很难再东山再起
...well then,that's pretty darn hard to recover from.
好，现在我紧张了
Okay,now I'm nervous.
也许你应该延期
Maybe you should put it off.
不，我不要延期！
No,I don't want to put it off!
我去年一整年都很悲惨
I spent last year being so unbelievably miserable.
现在我很快乐
And now I'm actually happy.
真的很快乐
You know,I mean really happy.
我不希望…
I just don't wanna....
我不希望搞砸了，你知道吧？
I don't wanna mess it up,you know?
我知道
I know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这又不是你的错
It's not your fault.
嗯…
Right.
也许不需要这么困难
Maybe it doesn't have to be this tough.
也许你顺其自然是对的
Maybe you were on the right track with that whole "spontaneous" thing.
女人真的喜欢这样 真的？
-Women really like that. -Really?
如果是我，我会希望你…
I mean if it were me,I'd want you to....
趁我没有防备的时候…
I don't know,catch me off guard with a really...
好好给我一个吻
...good kiss.
刚开始要很轻柔
Really sort of soft at first.
然后也许把我的头发拨开
And then maybe brush the hair away from my face.
凝视我的眼睛…
And then look far into my eyes...
让我知道有美妙的事情…
...in a way that lets me know something...
快要发生了
...amazing is about to happen.
然后，我不知道，然后…
And then,I don't know,then...
你会更紧地搂住我…
...you'd pull me really close to you so that...
我会紧紧帖着你…
...so that I'd be pressed up right against you.
然后就会开始…
And it would get kind of...
流汗…
...sweaty...
目眩神迷…
...and blurry.
一切就自然发生…
And then it's just happening.
谢谢，瑞秋，晚安！
Thanks,Rach. Good night!
天啊！
Oh,God!
《雨中曲》的插曲
早安！
Good morning!
昨晚有人爽到了！
Well,somebody got some last night!
两次！
Twice!